A Guide to the Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Collection, 1856-2019
Shenandoah County Library
- Series IX: Church Books
  - 38758101567294 Stack 10, Shelf 3 (Box 23)
    - “Our First Organ” Deems New and Easy Method for the Parlor Organ, 1885
    - “Our First Organ” Modern School for the Organ by C.E. Clemons, Evamay Miller’s Book, 1903
    - Book of Worship, Mary A. Swartz, 1915
    - “The Call to Praise” Children’s Hymnal, 1929
    - “Youth Hymnal” 1935
    - Lutheran Book of Prayer, 1951
    - Lutheran Service Book and Hymnal, Music Edition, Owned by William Parsons, Mt. Airy Seminary, 1958
    - Lutheran Service Book and Hymnal, 1958
    - Service Book and Hymnal, Athena Gochenour Confirmation, May 30 1971
    - “Our First Organ” Moller’s New Method of Instruction for the Reed Organ, Undated
    - “Our First Organ” Swan’s Instructor for the Reed Organ, Undated
  - 38758101567302 Stack 10, Shelf 2 (Box 24)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Weekly Offering Record Book, 1935-1937
    - Financial Contributions Record Book, 1938-1940
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Financial Contributions Record Book, 1941-1942
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church “Parish Records” 1947-1981
    - Weekly Offerings, 1949
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church “Our Church Guests” Book, 1949-2003
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Account Book, 1950-1953
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church “Treasurer’s Book,” 1959-1967
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church “Lutheran Book of Worship Minister’s Edition,” 1978
    - Virginia Lutheran Synod Assembly Minutes, 1999
    - Virginia Lutheran Synod Assembly Minutes, 2001
    - Virginia Lutheran Synod Assembly Minutes, 2003
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church 125th Anniversary Guest Book, 2009
- Series X: Audio/Visual Materials
  - 38758101567328 Stack 10, Shelf 3 (Box 25)
    - Audio-Visual Recording Mt. Zion 01 (Sleeve 25.1)
    - Audio-Visual Recording Mt. Zion 02 (Sleeve 25.2)
    - Audio-Visual Recording Mt. Zion 03 (Sleeve 25.3)
    - Audio-Visual Recording Mt. Zion 04 (Sleeve 25.4)
    - Audio-Visual Recording Mt. Zion 05 (Sleeve 25.5)
    - Audio-Visual Recording Mt. Zion 06 (Sleeve 25.6)
    - Audio-Visual Recording Mt. Zion 07 (Sleeve 25.7)
    - Audio-Visual Recording Mt. Zion 08 (Sleeve 25.8)
    - Audio-Visual Recording Mt. Zion 09 (Sleeve 25.9)
    - Audio-Visual Recording Mt. Zion 10 (Sleeve 25.10)
    - Audio-Visual Recording Mt. Zion 11 (Sleeve 25.11)
    - Audio-Visual Recording Mt. Zion 12 (Sleeve 25.12)
  - 38758101567336 Stack 10, Shelf 3 (Box 26)
    - Pastors of Mt. Zion, 1884-2007 (Box-folder 26.1)
    - Mt. Zion Golden Age Dinner, ca. 1970 (Box-folder 26.2)
    - Lucy Swartz, 1980 (Box-folder 26.3)
    - Richard M. Carbaugh, 1980 (Box-folder 26.4)
    - “Mt. Zion Dedication” Photograph, 1981 (Box-folder 26.5)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Congregation Photograph, 1997 (Box-folder 26.6)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Congregation Photograph, 2008 (Box-folder 26.7)
    - Combined St. Luke and Mt. Zion Choir, Undated (Box-folder 26.8)
  - 38758101567344 Stack 10, Shelf 3 (Box 27)
    - Postcard Depicting Mt. Zion Lutheran Church, Send to Ola Bly from Emma Wise, September 18, 1911 (Sleeve 27.1)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church (1 of 2), ca. 1920 (Sleeve 27.2)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church (2 of 2), ca. 1920 (Sleeve 27.3)
    - Confirmation, March 31 1957 (Sleeve 27.4)
    - Confirmation, March 31 1957 (Sleeve 27.5)
    - Massanetta Springs (1 of 3), 1957-1959 (Sleeve 27.6)
    - Massanetta Springs (2 of 3), 1957-1959 (Sleeve 27.7)
    - Massanetta Springs (3 of 3), 1957-1959 (Sleeve 27.8)
    - Meals (1 of 2), 1957-2011 (Sleeve 27.9)
    - Meals (2 of 2), 1957-2011 (Sleeve 27.10)
    - Massanetta Springs Postcards (1 of 3), ca. 1959 (Sleeve 27.11)
    - Massanetta Springs Postcards (2 of 3), ca. 1959 (Sleeve 27.12)
    - Massanetta Springs Postcards (2 of 3), ca. 1959 (Sleeve 27.13)
    - Confirmation, ca. 1962 (Sleeve 27.14)
    - “People” Unlabeled Church Photographs (1 of 3), 1964-2015 (Sleeve 27.15)
    - “People” Unlabeled Church Photographs (2 of 3), 1964-2015 (Sleeve 27.16)
    - “People” Unlabeled Church Photographs (3 of 3), 1964-2015 (Sleeve 27.17)
    - “People” Labeled Church Photographs (1 of 9), 1964-2015 (Sleeve 27.18)
    - “People” Labeled Church Photographs (2 of 9), 1964-2015 (Sleeve 27.19)
    - “People” Labeled Church Photographs (3 of 9), 1964-2015 (Sleeve 27.20)
    - “People” Labeled Church Photographs (4 of 9), 1964-2015 (Sleeve 27.21)
    - “People” Labeled Church Photographs (5 of 9), 1964-2015 (Sleeve 27.22)
    - “People” Labeled Church Photographs (6 of 9), 1964-2015 (Sleeve 27.23)
    - “People” Labeled Church Photographs (7 of 9), 1964-2015 (Sleeve 27.24)
    - “People” Labeled Church Photographs (8 of 9), 1964-2015 (Sleeve 27.25)
    - “People” Labeled Church Photographs (9 of 9), 1964-2015 (Sleeve 27.26)
    - Christmas, 1969 (Sleeve 27.27)
    - Bible School, June 1969 (Sleeve 27.28)
    - Church Parsonage, ca. 1970 (Sleeve 27.29)
    - Confirmation, May 30 1971 (Sleeve 27.30)
    - Christmas Photographic Card, 1971 (Sleeve 27.31)
    - Christmas Eve, 1971 (Sleeve 27.32)
    - “Mt. Zion Special Services,” 1973-1995 (Sleeve 27.33)
    - Confirmation, ca. 1974 (Sleeve 27.34)
    - Pastor Parsons and Family, 1975 (Sleeve 27.35)
    - Pastor Aubern Bowers, 1976 (Sleeve 27.36)
    - Confirmation, 1976 (Sleeve 27.37)
    - Pastor Ira Wilson, ca. 1976 (Sleeve 27.38)
    - Interior, Mt. Zion Lutheran Church, Christmas, Before 1980 (Sleeve 27.39)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church, Before 1980 (Sleeve 27.40)
    - “The Youth & Adults of Bible School,” June 15-19 1980 (Sleeve 27.41)
    - Ground breaking (1 of 3), June 29 1980 (Sleeve 27.42)
    - Ground breaking (2 of 3), June 29 1980 (Sleeve 27.43)
    - Ground breaking (3 of 3), June 29 1980 (Sleeve 27.44)
    - “The beginning of the building project,” July 6 1980 (Sleeve 27.45)
    - “The looks of the foundation,” July 13 1980 (Sleeve 27.46)
    - “The material for the project,” July 17 1980 (Sleeve 27.47)
    - “The beginning of the new basement of the new building,” July 17 1980 (Sleeve 27.48)
    - “The Church of Mt. Zion,” July 17 1980 (Sleeve 27.49)
    - “Our present parsonage as it stands today that was built in 1956,” July 17 1980 (Sleeve 27.50)
    - “Congregational Meeting to elect a new trustee of the church,” July 20 1980 (Sleeve 27.51)
    - Church Trustee, July 20 1980 (Sleeve 27.52)
    - “Building Project,” July 27 1980 (Sleeve 27.53)
    - “Building Project,” August 3 1980 (Sleeve 27.54)
    - “The building project,” August 10 1980 (Sleeve 27.55)
    - “The building project,” August 24-31 1980 (Sleeve 27.56)
    - “The building project,” August 31 1980 (Sleeve 27.57)
    - “The Oldest Carpenter of our church busy at his work,” August 31 1980 (Sleeve 27.58)
    - Building Project, August 31 1980 (Sleeve 27.59)
    - “Choir Members with New Robes,” September 6 1980 (Sleeve 27.60)
    - Building Project, September 6 1980 (Sleeve 27.61)
    - “Active Senior Citizens Brother & Sister Ben & Lucy Gochenour,” September 6 1980 (Sleeve 27.62)
    - “Our Electrician of Mt. Zion Bill Gochenour,” September 13 1980 (Sleeve 27.63)
    - Building Project, September 21 1980 (Sleeve 27.64)
    - “Special Called Meeting of the Council,” September 21 1980 (Sleeve 27.65)
    - Dunkles Grove Building, September 21 1980 (Sleeve 27.66)
    - “Oldest Married Couple of Mt. Zion Mr. & Mrs. Clint Reynolds,” Age 87 & 87, September 1980 (Sleeve 27.67)
    - Building Project, October 5 1980 (Sleeve 27.68)
    - Building Project, October 12 1980 (Sleeve 27.69)
    - Building Project, October 26 1980 (Sleeve 27.70)
    - Building Project, November 2 1980 (Sleeve 27.71)
    - “The Leveling of the Lawn and Parking Lot” Building Project, November 16 1980 (Sleeve 27.72)
    - Building Project, November 30 1980 (Sleeve 27.73)
    - Building Project, December 7 1980 (Sleeve 27.74)
    - Building Project, December 28 1980 (Sleeve 27.75)
    - “Mt. Zion LCW,” 1980 (Sleeve 27.76)
    - “Three generations of the Copp family that gave the land for the parking lot,” 1980 (Sleeve 27.77)
    - Pastor Richard M. Carbaugh and family, 1980 (Sleeve 27.78)
    - “Organist for Mt. Zion Edna Richard,” 1980 (Sleeve 27.79)
    - Christmas/Advent Decorations (1 of 2), 1980 (Sleeve 27.80)
    - Christmas/Advent Decorations (2 of 2), 1980 (Sleeve 27.81)
    - Vacation School (1 of 2), 1980 (Sleeve 27.82)
    - Vacation School (2 of 2), 1980 (Sleeve 27.83)
    - “The acolyte Boys who served as altar boys of Mt. Zion,” 1980 (Sleeve 27.84)
    - Betty Racey Mt. Zion Scrapbook (1 of 17), ca. 1980 (Sleeve 27.85)
    - Betty Racey Mt. Zion Scrapbook (2 of 17), ca. 1980 (Sleeve 27.86)
    - Betty Racey Mt. Zion Scrapbook (3 of 17), ca. 1980 (Sleeve 27.87)
    - Betty Racey Mt. Zion Scrapbook (4 of 17), ca. 1980 (Sleeve 27.88)
    - Betty Racey Mt. Zion Scrapbook (5 of 17), ca. 1980 (Sleeve 27.89)
    - Betty Racey Mt. Zion Scrapbook (6 of 17), ca. 1980 (Sleeve 27.90)
    - Betty Racey Mt. Zion Scrapbook (7 of 17), ca. 1980 (Sleeve 27.91)
    - Betty Racey Mt. Zion Scrapbook (8 of 17), ca. 1980 (Sleeve 27.92)
    - Betty Racey Mt. Zion Scrapbook (9 of 17), ca. 1980 (Sleeve 27.93)
    - Betty Racey Mt. Zion Scrapbook (10 of 17), ca. 1980 (Sleeve 27.94)
    - Betty Racey Mt. Zion Scrapbook (11 of 17), ca. 1980 (Sleeve 27.95)
    - Betty Racey Mt. Zion Scrapbook (12 of 17), ca. 1980 (Sleeve 27.96)
    - Betty Racey Mt. Zion Scrapbook (13 of 17), ca. 1980 (Sleeve 27.97)
    - Betty Racey Mt. Zion Scrapbook (14 of 17), ca. 1980 (Sleeve 27.98)
    - Betty Racey Mt. Zion Scrapbook (15 of 17), ca. 1980 (Sleeve 27.99)
    - Betty Racey Mt. Zion Scrapbook (16 of 17), ca. 1980 (Sleeve 27.100)
    - Betty Racey Mt. Zion Scrapbook (17 of 17), ca. 1980 (Sleeve 27.101)
    - Betty Racey Mt. Zion Scrapbook (1 of 6), ca. 1980 (Sleeve 27.102)
    - Betty Racey Mt. Zion Scrapbook (2 of 6), ca. 1980 (Sleeve 27.103)
    - Betty Racey Mt. Zion Scrapbook (3 of 6), ca. 1980 (Sleeve 27.104)
    - Betty Racey Mt. Zion Scrapbook (4 of 6), ca. 1980 (Sleeve 27.105)
    - Betty Racey Mt. Zion Scrapbook (5 of 6), ca. 1980 (Sleeve 27.106)
    - Betty Racey Mt. Zion Scrapbook (6 of 6), ca. 1980 (Sleeve 27.107)
    - Nursery Room and Pastor’s Study, February to March 1981 (Sleeve 27.108)
    - Annual Clean-up, Mt. Zion Church (1 of 3), March 10 1981 (Sleeve 27.109)
    - Annual Clean-up, Mt. Zion Church (2 of 3), March 10 1981 (Sleeve 27.110)
    - Annual Clean-up, Mt. Zion Church (3 of 3), March 10 1981 (Sleeve 27.111)
    - “Pastor Richard M. Carbaugh in his new study of the new building,” March 27 1981 (Sleeve 27.112)
    - Laying of the Cornerstone, April 12 1981 (Sleeve 27.112)
    - Church Council, April 12 1981 (Sleeve 27.113)
    - Building Committee, April 12 1981 (Sleeve 27.114)
    - Preparation of the Laying of the Cornerstone, April 12 1981 (Sleeve 27.115)
    - Betty Stultz, Secretary of the Cradle Roll, April 12 1981 (Sleeve 27.116)
    - Bobby Stultz, Church Trustee, April 12 1981 (Sleeve 27.117)
    - The Kitchen and Hall, April 28 1981 (Sleeve 27.118)
    - Olive Fravel, April 29 1981 (Sleeve 27.119)
    - Church Altar at the Dedication, May 3 1981 (Sleeve 27.120)
    - “Corner Display at the Dedication (1 of 3), May 3 1981 (Sleeve 27.121)
    - “Corner Display at the Dedication (2 of 3), May 3 1981 (Sleeve 27.122)
    - “Corner Display at the Dedication (3 of 3), May 3 1981 (Sleeve 27.123)
    - “Mt. Zion Lutheran Church in it’s completion,” May 3 1981 (Sleeve 27.124)
    - “Mt. Zion’s Dream-Now A Reality,” May 3 1981 (Sleeve 27.125)
    - Pastor Richard M. Carbaugh and Bishop Virgil Moyer Jr. Virginia Lutheran Synod, Building Dedication, May 3 1981 (Sleeve 27.126)
    - Flowers Donated for Dedication of Mt. Zion, May 3 1981 (Sleeve 27.127)
    - New Kitchen, 1981 (Sleeve 27.128)
    - “Present & Passed Sunday School Superintendent,” 1981 (Sleeve 27.129)
    - “Active Youngest Citizens Brother & Sister Eric & Jill Carbaugh,” 1981 (Sleeve 27.130)
    - Church Youth group (1 of 6), 1981-2002 (Sleeve 27.131)
    - Church Youth group (2 of 6), 1981-2002 (Sleeve 27.132)
    - Church Youth group (3 of 6), 1981-2002 (Sleeve 27.133)
    - Church Youth group (4 of 6), 1981-2002 (Sleeve 27.134)
    - Church Youth group (5 of 6), 1981-2002 (Sleeve 27.135)
    - Church Youth group (6 of 6), 1981-2002 (Sleeve 27.136)
    - “Pattie Lou entertaining at Birthday Dinner,” September 19 1982 (Sleeve 27.137)
    - Vacation Bible School (1 of 5), 1982 (Sleeve 27.138)
    - Vacation Bible School (2 of 5), 1982 (Sleeve 27.139)
    - Vacation Bible School (3 of 5), 1982 (Sleeve 27.140)
    - Vacation Bible School (4 of 5), 1982 (Sleeve 27.141)
    - Vacation Bible School (5 of 5), 1982 (Sleeve 27.142)
    - Vacation School (1 of 7), 1983 (Sleeve 27.143)
    - Vacation School (2 of 7), 1983 (Sleeve 27.144)
    - Vacation School (3 of 7), 1983 (Sleeve 27.145)
    - Vacation School (4 of 7), 1983 (Sleeve 27.146)
    - Vacation School (5 of 7), 1983 (Sleeve 27.147)
    - Vacation School (6 of 7), 1983 (Sleeve 27.148)
    - Vacation School (7 of 7), 1983 (Sleeve 27.149)
    - Adult Fellowship, 1986-1991 (Sleeve 27.150)
    - Renovation (1 of 4), May 1988 (Sleeve 27.151)
    - Renovation (2 of 4), May 1988 (Sleeve 27.152)
    - Renovation (3 of 4), May 1988 (Sleeve 27.153)
    - Renovation (4 of 4), May 1988 (Sleeve 27.154)
    - Nursery (1 of 3), 1989-1991 (Sleeve 27.155)
    - Nursery (2 of 3), 1989-1991 (Sleeve 27.156)
    - Nursery (3 of 3), 1989-1991 (Sleeve 27.157)
    - Easter Egg Hunt, April 1990 (Sleeve 27.158)
    - Youth Assembly (1 of 4), May 1990 (Sleeve 27.159)
    - Youth Assembly (2 of 4), May 1990 (Sleeve 27.160)
    - Youth Assembly (3 of 4), May 1990 (Sleeve 27.161)
    - Youth Assembly (4 of 4), May 1990 (Sleeve 27.162)
    - Water Activity (1 of 2), September 1990 (Sleeve 27.163)
    - Water Activity (2 of 2), September 1990 (Sleeve 27.164)
    - “Signs and Doors” (1 of 2), 1990 (Sleeve 27.165)
    - “Signs and Doors” (2 of 2), 1990 (Sleeve 27.166)
    - Power in the Spirit, 1990 (Sleeve 27.167)
    - Bible School (1 of 11), 1990 (Sleeve 27.168)
    - Bible School (2 of 11), 1990 (Sleeve 27.169)
    - Bible School (3 of 11), 1990 (Sleeve 27.170)
  - 38758101567351 Stack 10, Shelf 3 (Box 28)
    - Bible School (4 of 11), 1990 (Sleeve 28.1)
    - Bible School (5 of 11), 1990 (Sleeve 28.2)
    - Bible School (6 of 11), 1990 (Sleeve 28.3)
    - Bible School (7 of 11), 1990 (Sleeve 28.4)
    - Bible School (8 of 11), 1990 (Sleeve 28.5)
    - Bible School (9 of 11), 1990 (Sleeve 28.6)
    - Bible School (10 of 11), 1990 (Sleeve 28.7)
    - Bible School (11 of 11), 1990 (Sleeve 28.8)
    - “Outdoor Picnic?” (1 of 8), ca. 1990 (Sleeve 28.9)
    - “Outdoor Picnic?” (2 of 8), ca. 1990 (Sleeve 28.10)
    - “Outdoor Picnic?” (3 of 8), ca. 1990 (Sleeve 28.11)
    - “Outdoor Picnic?” (4 of 8), ca. 1990 (Sleeve 28.12)
    - “Outdoor Picnic?” (5 of 8), ca. 1990 (Sleeve 28.13)
    - “Outdoor Picnic?” (6 of 8), ca. 1990 (Sleeve 28.14)
    - “Outdoor Picnic?” (7 of 8), ca. 1990 (Sleeve 28.15)
    - “Outdoor Picnic?” (8 of 8), ca. 1990 (Sleeve 28.16)
    - “Bible School 2” (Labeled Church Photographs) (1 of 6), 1990-2000 (Sleeve 28.17)
    - “Bible School 2” (Labeled Church Photographs) (2 of 6), 1990-2000 (Sleeve 28.18)
    - “Bible School 2” (Labeled Church Photographs) (3 of 6), 1990-2000 (Sleeve 28.19)
    - “Bible School 2” (Labeled Church Photographs) (4 of 6), 1990-2000 (Sleeve 28.20)
    - “Bible School 2” (Labeled Church Photographs) (5 of 6), 1990-2000 (Sleeve 28.21)
    - “Bible School 2” (Labeled Church Photographs) (6 of 6), 1990-2000 (Sleeve 28.22)
    - Water Activity (1 of 4), August 15 1991 (Sleeve 28.23)
    - Water Activity (2 of 4), August 15 1991 (Sleeve 28.24)
    - Water Activity (3 of 4), August 15 1991 (Sleeve 28.25)
    - Water Activity (4 of 4), August 15 1991 (Sleeve 28.26)
    - “Heifer Project/March of Dimes” (1 of 2), October 1991 (Sleeve 28.27)
    - “Heifer Project/March of Dimes” (2 of 2), October 1991 (Sleeve 28.28)
    - “?Martha Project” (1 of 2), October 1991 (Sleeve 28.29)
    - “?Martha Project” (2 of 2), October 1991 (Sleeve 28.30)
    - “St. Nicholas Story” Mt. Zion Lutheran Church (1 of 2), November 30 1991 (Sleeve 28.31)
    - “St. Nicholas Story” Mt. Zion Lutheran Church (2 of 2), November 30 1991 (Sleeve 28.32)
    - Kitchen Ladies (1 of 3), 1991 (Sleeve 28.33)
    - Kitchen Ladies (2 of 3), 1991 (Sleeve 28.34)
    - Kitchen Ladies (3 of 3), 1991 (Sleeve 28.35)
    - Congregation (1 of 3), ca. 1991 (Sleeve 28.36)
    - Congregation (2 of 3), ca. 1991 (Sleeve 28.37)
    - Congregation (3 of 3), ca. 1991 (Sleeve 28.38)
    - Bowling Alley (1 of 5), ca. 1991 (Sleeve 28.39)
    - Bowling Alley (2 of 5), ca. 1991 (Sleeve 28.40)
    - Bowling Alley (3 of 5), ca. 1991 (Sleeve 28.41)
    - Bowling Alley (4 of 5), ca. 1991 (Sleeve 28.42)
    - Bowling Alley (5 of 5), ca. 1991 (Sleeve 28.43)
    - Adult Classes (1 of 2), ca. 1991 (Sleeve 28.44)
    - Adult Classes (2 of 2), ca. 1991 (Sleeve 28.45)
    - Animals (1 of 4), ca. 1991 (Sleeve 28.46)
    - Animals (2 of 4), ca. 1991 (Sleeve 28.47)
    - Animals (3 of 4), ca. 1991 (Sleeve 28.48)
    - Animals (4 of 4), ca. 1991 (Sleeve 28.49)
    - “Mt. Zion Happenings” (1 of 3), 1991-1992 (Sleeve 28.50)
    - “Mt. Zion Happenings” (2 of 3), 1991-1992 (Sleeve 28.51)
    - “Mt. Zion Happenings” (3 of 3), 1991-1992 (Sleeve 28.52)
    - Frontier Culture Museum-Adult Trips (1 of 3), 1991-1994 (Sleeve 28.53)
    - Frontier Culture Museum-Adult Trips (2 of 3), 1991-1994 (Sleeve 28.54)
    - Frontier Culture Museum-Adult Trips (3 of 3), 1991-1994 (Sleeve 28.55)
    - Heifer Project (1 of 5), January 1992 (Sleeve 28.56)
    - Heifer Project (2 of 5), January 1992 (Sleeve 28.57)
    - Heifer Project (3 of 5), January 1992 (Sleeve 28.58)
    - Heifer Project (4 of 5), January 1992 (Sleeve 28.59)
    - Heifer Project (5 of 5), January 1992 (Sleeve 28.60)
    - Basket Making WELCA Retreat (1 of 2), September 1992 (Sleeve 28.61)
    - Basket Making WELCA Retreat (2 of 2), September 1992 (Sleeve 28.62)
    - Power in the Spirit, 1992 (Sleeve 28.63)
    - People #2 (1 of 13), ca. 1992 (Sleeve 28.64)
    - People #2 (2 of 13), ca. 1992 (Sleeve 28.65)
    - People #2 (3 of 13), ca. 1992 (Sleeve 28.66)
    - People #2 (4 of 13), ca. 1992 (Sleeve 28.67)
    - People #2 (5 of 13), ca. 1992 (Sleeve 28.68)
    - People #2 (6 of 13), ca. 1992 (Sleeve 28.69)
    - People #2 (7 of 13), ca. 1992 (Sleeve 28.70)
    - People #2 (8 of 13), ca. 1992 (Sleeve 28.71)
    - People #2 (9 of 13), ca. 1992 (Sleeve 28.72)
    - People #2 (10 of 13), ca. 1992 (Sleeve 28.73)
    - People #2 (11 of 13), ca. 1992 (Sleeve 28.74)
    - People #2 (12 of 13), ca. 1992 (Sleeve 28.75)
    - People #2 (13 of 13), ca. 1992 (Sleeve 28.76)
    - “Celebration?” (1 of 4), July 1993 (Sleeve 28.77)
    - “Celebration?” (2 of 4), July 1993 (Sleeve 28.78)
    - “Celebration?” (3 of 4), July 1993 (Sleeve 28.79)
    - “Celebration?” (4 of 4), July 1993 (Sleeve 28.80)
    - Power in the Spirit, 1993 (Sleeve 28.81)
    - Paving Lot, 1994 (Sleeve 28.82)
    - Power in the Spirit (1 of 2), 1995 (Sleeve 28.83)
    - Power in the Spirit (2 of 2), 1995 (Sleeve 28.84)
    - “Sunday in the Park, 4:00PM Until ?” (1 of 4), July 26 1998 (Sleeve 28.85)
    - “Sunday in the Park, 4:00PM Until ?” (2 of 4), July 26 1998 (Sleeve 28.86)
    - “Sunday in the Park, 4:00PM Until ?” (3 of 4), July 26 1998 (Sleeve 28.87)
    - “Sunday in the Park, 4:00PM Until ?” (4 of 4), July 26 1998 (Sleeve 28.88)
    - New Windsor Church World Relief (1 of 2), July 1999 (Sleeve 28.89)
    - New Windsor Church World Relief (2 of 2), July 1999 (Sleeve 28.90)
    - Family Picnic (1 of 10), 1999 (Sleeve 28.91)
    - Family Picnic (2 of 10), 1999 (Sleeve 28.92)
    - Family Picnic (3 of 10), 1999 (Sleeve 28.93)
    - Family Picnic (4 of 10), 1999 (Sleeve 28.94)
    - Family Picnic (5 of 10), 1999 (Sleeve 28.95)
    - Family Picnic (6 of 10), 1999 (Sleeve 28.96)
    - Family Picnic (7 of 10), 1999 (Sleeve 28.97)
    - Family Picnic (8 of 10), 1999 (Sleeve 28.98)
    - Family Picnic (9 of 10), 1999 (Sleeve 28.99)
    - Family Picnic (10 of 10), 1999 (Sleeve 28.100)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church WELCA Family Night (1 of 3), 1999 (Sleeve 28.101)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church WELCA Family Night (2 of 3), 1999 (Sleeve 28.102)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church WELCA Family Night (3 of 3), 1999 (Sleeve 28.103)
    - Activity Photographs (1 of 3), ca. 1999 (Sleeve 28.104)
    - Activity Photographs (2 of 3), ca. 1999 (Sleeve 28.105)
    - Activity Photographs (3 of 3), ca. 1999 (Sleeve 28.106)
    - “Men of the Church Serving the Women” Mother’s Day (1 of 2), 2000 (Sleeve 28.107)
    - “Men of the Church Serving the Women” Mother’s Day (2 of 2), 2000 (Sleeve 28.108)
    - “Visiting Missionary,” May 2002 (Sleeve 28.109)
    - WELCA Ladies Night Out, June 2000 (Sleeve 28.110)
    - Unidentified Church Event 2 (1 of 3), December 2002 (Sleeve 28.111)
    - Unidentified Church Event 2 (2 of 3), December 2002 (Sleeve 28.112)
    - Unidentified Church Event 2 (3 of 3), December 2002 (Sleeve 28.113)
    - Unidentified Church Event (1 of 2), May 17 2003 (Sleeve 28.114)
    - Unidentified Church Event (2 of 2), May 17 2003 (Sleeve 28.115)
    - Outdoor Sunday Maurertown Park (1 of 3), 2003 (Sleeve 28.116)
    - Outdoor Sunday Maurertown Park (2 of 3), 2003 (Sleeve 28.117)
    - Outdoor Sunday Maurertown Park (3 of 3), 2003 (Sleeve 28.118)
    - Confirmation, 2004 (Sleeve 28.119)
    - “Church” (Negatives), 2004 (Sleeve 28.120)
    - “Join the Navey” Liturgical Dance, Summer 2005 (Sleeve 28.121)
    - WELCA (1 of 2), ca. 2005 (Sleeve 28.122)
    - WELCA (2 of 2), ca. 2005 (Sleeve 28.123)
    - “Dukie Racey’s Bluegrass Band,” Undated (Sleeve 28.124)
    - “Mt. Zion’s Future” Unidentified Children’s Activities (1 of 2), Undated (Sleeve 28.125)
    - “Mt. Zion’s Future” Unidentified Children’s Activities (2 of 2), Undated (Sleeve 28.126)
    - Breakfast at Church, Male Servers (1 of 2), Undated (Sleeve 28.127)
    - Breakfast at Church, Male Servers (2 of 2), Undated (Sleeve 28.128)
    - Men Preparing a Meal (1 of 2), Undated (Sleeve 28.129)
    - Men Preparing a Meal (2 of 2), Undated (Sleeve 28.130)
    - “Kids” (1 of 3), Undated (Sleeve 28.131)
    - “Kids” (2 of 3), Undated (Sleeve 28.132)
    - “Kids” (3 of 3), Undated (Sleeve 28.133)
    - Church Service Interpretative Dance (1 of 2), Undated (Sleeve 28.134)
    - Church Service Interpretative Dance (2 of 2), Undated (Sleeve 28.135)
    - Choir (1 of 2), Undated (Sleeve 28.136)
    - Choir (2 of 2), Undated (Sleeve 28.137)
    - "Trust In God” Banner, Undated (Sleeve 28.138)
    - “Talent Night” (1 of 4), Undated (Sleeve 28.139)
    - “Talent Night” (2 of 4), Undated (Sleeve 28.140)
    - “Talent Night” (3 of 4), Undated (Sleeve 28.141)
    - “Talent Night” (4 of 4), Undated (Sleeve 28.142)
    - Pastor Orell and Family, Undated (Sleeve 28.143)
    - “Pastor Scott,” Undated (Sleeve 28.144)
    - “Pastor Carbaugh & Family,” Undated (Sleeve 28.145)
    - “Blessing of the Animals Pastor Scott & Pastor Butler from Patmos/St. Luke,” Undated (Sleeve 28.146)
    - Vacation Bible School, Undated (Sleeve 28.147)
    - Choir Pictures, Undated (Sleeve 28.148)
    - Church Trustees, Undated (Sleeve 28.149)
    - Power in the Spirit, Undated (Sleeve 28.150)
    - Power in the Spirit, Undated (Sleeve 28.151)
    - “Other Entertainment,” Undated (Sleeve 28.152)
    - “Hand Chimes The Ding-a-Lings” (1 of 2), Undated (Sleeve 28.153)
    - “Hand Chimes The Ding-a-Lings” (2 of 2), Undated (Sleeve 28.154)
    - “Walkers p. 31,” Undated (Sleeve 28.155)
    - “Picnic?” (1 of 5), Undated (Sleeve 28.156)
    - “Picnic?” (2 of 5), Undated (Sleeve 28.157)
    - “Picnic?” (3 of 5), Undated (Sleeve 28.158)
    - “Picnic?” (4 of 5), Undated (Sleeve 28.159)
    - “Picnic?” (5 of 5), Undated (Sleeve 28.160)
    - Confirmation, Undated (Sleeve 28.161)